<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TB portfolio</title>
    <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TB portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.tor-bjorn.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Utblick no.2</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/utblick-no.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/utblick-no.2/</guid>
      <description>Description of heroimage About The theme for this number of Utblick Magazine was Responsibility and Growth on different levels. Illustrations of plants and greenery was made and used throughout the number.&#xA;The magazine was printed on a uncoated paper using two Pantone colors and black.&#xA;Role Art Direction and Illustration&#xA;Title here My quote Ullamco aliqua quis consequat duis proident eu laborum. Incididunt ad eu cupidatat mollit. Enim duis voluptate exercitation id cupidatat labore nulla esse do consectetur sint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cut up World</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/a-cut-up-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/a-cut-up-world/</guid>
      <description>About An exploration of our time and the borderland between two worlds. How they differ; but also how they draw near to one another. An investigation of how the internet and the tools we use daily can be used to create a story.&#xA;Role Graphic designer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gothenburg Poster</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/gothenburg-poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/gothenburg-poster/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the City</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/in-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/in-the-city/</guid>
      <description> About The theme for this number of Utblick Magazine was Responsibility and Growth on different levels. Illustrations of plants and greenery was made and used throughout the number.&#xA;The magazine was printed on a uncoated paper using two Pantone colors and black.&#xA;Role Art Direction and Illustration&#xA;Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here Title here </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utblick no.4</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/utblick-no.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/utblick-no.4/</guid>
      <description>About The theme for this number of Utblick Magazine was Responsibility and Growth on different levels. Illustrations of plants and greenery was made and used throughout the number.&#xA;The magazine was printed on a uncoated paper using two Pantone colors and black.&#xA;Role Art Direction and Illustration&#xA;Title here My quote Ullamco aliqua quis consequat duis proident eu laborum. Incididunt ad eu cupidatat mollit. Enim duis voluptate exercitation id cupidatat labore nulla esse do consectetur sint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things in a Conversation</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/things-in-a-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/works/things-in-a-conversation/</guid>
      <description>About Conversing is probably not an activity that would be expected between any objects, hence it breaks with certain preconceived expectations. Both in how the objects could be understood, but also in how the perception of the conversation is to be interpreted in this situation. What are they, and what are they talking about?&#xA;Role Design and manufacturing of artifacts with CNC and wood work craft tools. Design and production of sprial book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Send me a message Name Email Address Subject Message Send message Torbjörn Hedberg Gökevägen 14 422 43 Hisings Backa&#xA;hej@tor-bjorn.com +46 (0) 702 - 56 20 90&#xA;Newsletter Subscribe to newsletter for news and update when new content is added to the site.&#xA;Email Address </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Product designer based in Gothenburg. Specialized in graphic design with a focus on UI/UX. Hi! My name is Torbjörn Hedberg. As of now, I’m primarily involved in the process of bringing ideas to realization in the form of user interfaces for the web and mobile applications. I do, however, have a rich background in the field of visual communication, working with projects in print design, illustrations and animations.&#xA;Through my work as a designer I tackle problems on different levels; always with the goal of creating a user friendly products and solutions that are joyfull.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Subscribe to my newsletter for news and be notified when new content is added to the site. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you</title>
      <link>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.tor-bjorn.com/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for getting in touch! I’ll get back to you as soon as possible. Newsletter Subscribe to newsletter for news and update when new content is added to the site.&#xA;Email Address </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
